satyapaul.com 2017-07-20

# Privacy Policy

##### Policy

Satya Paul provides this privacy policy to describe how we use and process certain information that we obtain through the web site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any data that we collect offline or through sources other than this Site. Satya Paul is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizes your need to protect the personal information that you share with us on this web site.

##### Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes, we will post a revised version of the Privacy Policy on the Site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any data to us.

##### Types of Data processed

We collect certain individually identifiable data that you actively submit through the Site as well as other non-individually identifiable information that we collect through tracking technologies.

You may purchase products, sign up for a newsletter, participate in promotions, or otherwise actively send us personal data on the Site. Such personal data may include your name, email address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, credit card information, consumption patterns, lifestyle, and product interests.

##### Disclaimer

All policies are subject to change without prior notice. In case of any conflict Terms of use Policy would prevail.

##### Purpose and Sharing of Data

Satya Paul will use this data to provide better service to Site visitors, customize the Site based on your preferences, compile and analyze statistics and trends, to otherwise administer and improve the site for your use,and to personalize offers. We may also use personal data to transmit direct marketing communications to you by email, although you can opt-out of receiving such communications at any time.

We do not disclose your personal data to third parties, unless required by law, necessary in connection with a legal claim or proceeding, or when otherwise necessary to protect the rights or interests of Satya Paul.

##### Correction and control of data

Please keep your personal data, accurate, current, and complete by regularly updating your personal account or by contacting us at customercare@satyapaul.com If you later object to the use of your personal information (for example, you no longer wish to receive promotional or marketing information about products, services, and offerings from Satya Paul or any third parties) you can cancel your Satya Paul member account. Simply send an email message to our customer care and be sure to indicate 'UNSUBSCRIBE' in the subject line. Your request will be processed as soon as possible. Please bear in mind that cancellation of your member account will result in you not being able to access the relevant services, offers or content.

##### Security Statement

Transmission of information via the internet is unfortunately not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal data we cannot guarantee the security of your data submitted to us and any transmission is at your own risk.
